Muse over the antique memories
Realize again every fragment shown to know why
On my ugly dress in the millions of laughs occurs
Fool me but I could and I act like show is luxury
A
A fantasy
For a long time, this body burned in the fire
Asking for the meaning of the truth
本当の二十歳の意味を尋ねて本当の二十歳の意味を尋ねて
それが人の汲めた呪いでもそれが人の汲めた呪いでも
心が夢る名は咲かせましょう心が夢る名は咲かせましょう
それでも世が愛しい神様らは悪い
壊れたと想像するほど生命線が座ってばかりで
花びらが柔らかい毒薬の味が
忘れられておられるまで
忘れられておられるまで囚われていたい
Chantelle, egg, flowers,
pick from my balm
Hitoriko, tsumuete no kurishin
My love for Brazil,
your vital human heart
Mayu no naka de umarete kita, nagai wa doku
声も目黒もないこの場所で
朧に映る影に見とれてる
それが人の喰うまた呪いでも
私にくれる Let's make it bloom
Even so, I don't know
God's words and love The more I think about it
The more I can't live The petals are soft
The taste of poison Thank you so much for watching this video, and I'll see you
in the next video!